Voices of Civil Rights Project collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series I: Manuscripts, 2003-2006
  - Subseries II: Submissions, 2003-2004, 1612 folders
    - Shaw, Ruth S. (Box-folder 19/21)
    - Shaw, Sondra Ann (Box-folder 19/22)
    - Shaw, Terry (Box-folder 19/23)
    - Sheffield, Wesley (Box-folder 19/24)
    - Shelby, Jerry L. (Box-folder 19/25)
    - Shell, Nancy K. (Box-folder 19/26)
    - Shepard, Rob (Box-folder 19/27)
    - Shepherd, Frankie Ferguson (Box-folder 19/28)
    - Sheppard, Jane S. (Box-folder 19/29)
    - Sheviakov, Rick (Box-folder 19/30)
    - Shier, Maurice S. (Box-folder 19/31)
    - Shine, George Dennis, Jr. (Box-folder 19/32)
    - Shishima, Bill (Box-folder 19/33)
    - Shockley, Charles C. (Box-folder 19/34)
    - Siederbaum, Harvey (Box-folder 19/35)
    - Silva, Victor (Box-folder 19/36)
    - Silverstein, Clara (Box-folder 19/37)
    - Simmons, Charlene (Box-folder 19/38)
    - Simmons, Verma J. (Box-folder 19/39)
    - Simmons-Mitchell, Mary Miaisha (Box-folder 19/40)
    - Simms, Carolyn P. (Box-folder 19/41)
    - Simms, Donald, Sr. (Box-folder 19/42)
    - Simpson, Robert J. (Box-folder 19/43)
    - Simpson, Robin Lee (Box-folder 19/44)
    - Simpson, Sue E. (Box-folder 19/45)
    - Sims, Lark (Box-folder 19/46)
    - Sims, Sheila C. (Box-folder 19/47)
    - Sisson, John P. (Box-folder 19/48)
    - Sivon, Richard (Box-folder 19/49)
    - Skinner, Clementine (Box-folder 19/50)
      Includes correspondence, photographs and news clippings.
    - Slate, Arthur J. (Box-folder 19/51)
    - Slaughter, Katherine E. (Box-folder 19/52)
    - Slaughter, Patricia (Box-folder 19/53)
    - Slemmer, Anna (Box-folder 19/54)
    - Slife-Thomas, Barbara J. (Box-folder 19/55)
    - Sloan, Barbara (Box-folder 19/56)
    - Sloan, Lester (Box-folder 19/57)
    - Smirni, Beverly Ann (Box-folder 19/58)
    - Smith, Barbara Leary (Box-folder 19/59)
    - Smith, Dallas R. (Box-folder 19/60)
    - Smith, Emerson (Box-folder 19/61)
    - Smith, Emily (Box-folder 19/62)
    - Smith, Jean O. (Box-folder 19/63)
    - Smith, Jeanie (Box-folder 19/64)
    - Smith, Jerry E. (Box-folder 19/65)
    - Smith, Joyce Harkleroad (Box-folder 19/66)
    - Smith, Keith (Box-folder 19/67)
    - Smith, Linda W. (Box-folder 19/68)
    - Smith, Marie I. (Box-folder 19/69)
    - Smith, Mary E. (Box-folder 19/70)
    - Smith, Melvin (Box-folder 19/71)
    - Smith, Myrielle (Box-folder 19/72)
    - Smith, Vernon E. (Box-folder 19/73)
    - Smith, Wilma J. (Box-folder 19/74)
    - Smith-Cullins, Tresa (Box-folder 19/75)
    - Snipes, Olivia (Box-folder 19/76)
    - Snyder, Paul W. (Box-folder 19/77)
    - Sobin, Donald (Box-folder 19/78)
    - Sorrell, James Robert (Box-folder 19/79)
    - Soto, Norma M. (Box-folder 19/80)
    - Spaulding, Julia (Box-folder 19/81)
    - Spear, Marion W. (Box-folder 19/82)
    - Spearman, Gloria (Box-folder 19/83)
    - Spears, Onnie H. (Box-folder 19/84)
    - Spencer, B. (Box-folder 19/85)
    - Spencer, Jennifer (Box-folder 19/86)
    - Spencer, Mickey (Box-folder 19/87)
    - Spencer, Russell (Box-folder 19/88)
    - Sporl, Mark J. (Box-folder 19/89)
    - Spurlock, Albert C. (Box-folder 19/90)
    - Staas, Beth (Box-folder 19/91)
    - Staley, Violet (Box-folder 19/92)
    - Stallworth, Howard (Box-folder 19/93)
    - Standard, Lawrence E. (Box-folder 19/94)
    - Starks, Margie N. (Box-folder 19/95)
    - Stauber, Linda (Box-folder 20/1)
    - Stelter, Donna M. (Box-folder 20/2)
    - Stephens, Dayle (Box-folder 20/3)
    - Stephens, John O. (Box-folder 20/4)
    - Stepteau, Dorothy M. (Box-folder 20/5)
    - Stevens, Alonzo (Box-folder 20/6)
    - Stevenson-Smith, Fay (Box-folder 20/7)
    - Steward, Ralph F. (Box-folder 20/8)
    - Stewart, Patricia (Box-folder 20/9)
    - Stewart, Willie C. (Box-folder 20/10)
    - Stiles, Lindley J. (Box-folder 20/11)
    - Stitt, Dorothy (Box-folder 20/12)
    - Stokes, Carolyn Ashe (Box-folder 20/13)
    - Stokes, Whitworth (Box-folder 20/14)
    - Straw, Derrick (Box-folder 20/15)
    - Strean, Marcia (Box-folder 20/16)
    - Sturdivant, Calvin E. (Box-folder 20/17)
    - Suddith, Beulah D. (Box-folder 20/18)
    - Suit, Randall D. (Box-folder 20/19)
    - Sussman, Harris (Box-folder 20/20)
    - Sutton, Goodloe (Box-folder 20/21)
    - Svensson, Marlys (Box-folder 20/22)
    - Swan, Janice (Box-folder 20/23)
    - Tafolla, Carmen (Box-folder 20/24)
    - Taft, Barbara (Box-folder 20/25)
    - Taliaferro, Lenore F. (Box-folder 20/26)
    - Taliferro, Charles (Box-folder 20/27)
    - Talley, Barbara (Box-folder 20/28)
    - Tani, Midori (Box-folder 20/29)
    - Tapper, Joyce N. (Box-folder 20/30)
    - Tatum, John W. (Box-folder 20/31)
    - Taylor, Ann Cannon (Box-folder 20/32)
    - Taylor, Brian (Box-folder 20/33)
    - Taylor, Charles (Box-folder 20/34)
    - Taylor, Gerard (Box-folder 20/35)
    - Taylor, Huldah E. (Box-folder 20/36)
    - Taylor, Janet B. (Box-folder 20/37)
    - Taylor, Joel S. (Box-folder 20/38)
      Includes essay and other writings.
    - Taylor, Ruth L. (Box-folder 20/39)
    - Teel, James (Box-folder 20/40)
    - Terrell, Ernest B. (Box-folder 20/41)
    - Thaler, Selma (Box-folder 20/42)
    - Tharalson, Mary Eileen (Box-folder 20/43)
    - Therkelson, Norma (Box-folder 20/44)
    - Thomas, Elnora (Box-folder 20/45)
    - Thomas, George (Box-folder 20/46)
    - Thomas, Jesse (Box-folder 20/47)
    - Thomas, Nathan, Jr. (Box-folder 20/48)
    - Thomas, Ophelia (Box-folder 20/49)
    - Thomas, Patricia (Box-folder 20/50)
    - Thomas, Alindra (Box-folder 20/51)
    - Thompson, Annie R. (Box-folder 20/52)
    - Thompson, Barbara Guillory (Box-folder 20/53)
    - Thompson, Faye W. (Box-folder 20/54)
    - Thompson, Helene (Box-folder 20/55)
    - Thompson, Herman G. (Box-folder 20/56)
    - Thompson, Jan (Box-folder 20/57)
    - Thompson, Mildred (Box-folder 20/58)
    - Thompson, Moses (Box-folder 20/59)
    - Thompson, Rosa L. (Box-folder 20/60)
    - Thompson, S. F. (Box-folder 20/61)
      Includes news clippings, certificate, correspondence, and memorandum.
    - Thomson, Betty Turner (Box-folder 20/62)
    - Thorne, Juanita Carter (Box-folder 20/63)
    - Thrasher, Dennis (Box-folder 20/64)
    - Threlkeld, Sandra (Box-folder 20/65)
    - Thurmond, Barbara (Box-folder 20/66)
    - Tiago, Giresse (Box-folder 20/67)
    - Timberlake, Constance A. (Box-folder 20/68)
    - Tindall, Gwendolyn (Box-folder 20/69)
    - Tinsley, Rita R. (Box-folder 20/70)
    - Tippett, Sandy (Box-folder 20/71)
    - Tipton, Mary E. (Box-folder 20/72)
    - Tisdale, Alice (Box-folder 20/73)
    - Tisdale, Charles (Box-folder 20/74)
    - Tisher, Lewis (Box-folder 20/75)
    - Todacheene, GloJean (Box-folder 20/76)
    - Todd, J. Lee (Box-folder 20/77)
    - Todd, Lois Faye (Box-folder 20/78)
    - Todd, Ophelia Tolbert (Box-folder 20/79)
    - Todd-Noches, Nancy (Box-folder 20/80)
    - Tolbert, Alphonso J. (Box-folder 20/81)
    - Tomas, Noel E. (Box-folder 20/82)
      Includes biography and article.
    - Tompkins, Nelson M. (Box-folder 21/1)
    - Toner, Thomas D. (Box-folder 21/2)
    - Tornay, Peter C. (Box-folder 21/3)
    - Torres, Guillermo (Box-folder 21/4)
    - Toulas, Maria (Box-folder 21/5)
    - Tow, Maxwell (Box-folder 21/6)
    - Townsend, Earl D. (Box-folder 21/7)
    - Townsend, Elizabeth (Box-folder 21/8)
    - Townsley, Richard (Box-folder 21/9)
    - Tracton, James B. (Box-folder 21/10)
    - Tramel, Linda (Box-folder 21/11)
    - Travaglini, Linda (Box-folder 21/12)
    - Trotter, Jane B. (Box-folder 21/13)
    - Trotter, Richard (Box-folder 21/14)
    - Trowbridge, Duaine E. (Box-folder 21/15)
    - Turnage, Martha A. (Box-folder 21/16)
    - Ullah, Sandra (Box-folder 21/17)
    - Underwood, Joseph J., Jr. (Box-folder 21/18)
    - Valdez, Frank (Box-folder 21/19)
    - Vambery, Renate (Box-folder 21/20)
    - Van Deusen, Roland (Box-folder 21/21)
    - Van Wormer, Katherine (Box-folder 21/22)
      Includes article.
    - Vance, Sharon (Box-folder 21/23)
    - VanderVeer, Jane (Box-folder 21/24)
    - VanSluytman, Stalburn A. (Box-folder 21/25)
    - Vasquez, Dennis A. (Box-folder 21/26)
    - Vigne, Elayne (Box-folder 21/27)
    - Villa, José D. (Box-folder 21/28)
    - Villegas, Alfredo (Box-folder 21/29)
    - Vivante, Bella (Box-folder 21/30)
    - Volnek, Katie (Box-folder 21/31)
    - Vreeland, Joella (Box-folder 21/32)
    - Wachob, Susan (Box-folder 21/33)
    - Wagner, Ted (Box-folder 21/34)
    - Walk, Rina (Box-folder 21/35)
    - Walker, Arthette Stafford (Box-folder 21/36)
    - Walker, Donald D. (Box-folder 21/37)
    - Walker, Margaret L. (Box-folder 21/38)
    - Walker, Nancy (Box-folder 21/39)
    - Walker, Nora C. (Box-folder 21/40)
    - Walker, Phillip (Box-folder 21/41)
    - Wallace, Pete (Box-folder 21/42)
    - Walton, Dorothy (Box-folder 21/43)
    - Walton, Ida Mae (Box-folder 21/44)
    - Ward, Andrew (Box-folder 21/45)
    - Ward, Joe (Box-folder 21/46)
    - Ward, Toni (Box-folder 21/47)
    - Warner, Victoria E. (Box-folder 21/48)
    - Warner-Stalling, Kathryn (Box-folder 21/49)
    - Warnock, Kresha (Box-folder 21/50)
    - Warren, Roberta M. (Box-folder 21/51)
    - Warren, Vickie (Box-folder 21/52)
    - Washington, Joan L. (Box-folder 21/53)
    - Washington, Rosa (Box-folder 21/54)
    - Washington-Lloyd, Emelda (Box-folder 21/55)
    - Washington-Risher, Sharon (Box-folder 21/56)
    - Wason, Martha M. (Box-folder 21/57)
    - Watermann, Fannie Delores (Box-folder 21/58)
    - Watford, Charles (Box-folder 21/59)
    - Watson, Vera E. (Box-folder 21/60)
    - Watt, S. Patricia (Box-folder 21/61)
    - Watts, Ophelia M. (Box-folder 21/62)
    - Waynick, Jack T. (Box-folder 21/63)
    - Weaver, Bernadette (Box-folder 21/64)
    - Weaver, Donald L. (Box-folder 21/65)
    - Weaver, Robert (Box-folder 21/66)
    - Webb, Earnest E. (Box-folder 21/67)
    - Webb, Karen Anne (Box-folder 21/68)
    - Webber, Clemmie E. (Box-folder 21/69)
    - Weber, Gretchen (Box-folder 21/70)
    - Weems, Eleanor Olsen (Box-folder 21/71)
    - Weigel, Keith V. (Box-folder 21/72)
    - Weisman, Seymour (Box-folder 21/73)
    - Weiss, Richard (Box-folder 21/74)
    - Welcome, Charles (Box-folder 21/75)
    - Wells, Lisa (Box-folder 21/76)
    - Wertheim, Charles D. (Box-folder 21/77)
    - Werthing, Sallie M. (Box-folder 21/78)
    - Wesley, Theressa Gunnels (Box-folder 21/79)
    - West, O. David (Box-folder 21/80)
    - West, Robert W. (Box-folder 21/81)
    - Westen, Morris (Box-folder 21/82)
    - Wheaton, Stephanie (Box-folder 21/83)
    - Wheeler, Janie M. (Box-folder 21/84)
    - Wheeler, Perry (Box-folder 21/85)
    - White, Barry Q. (Box-folder 21/86)
    - White, Brenda Joyce (Box-folder 21/87)
    - White, David Allen (Box-folder 21/88)
    - White, Robert E. (Box-folder 21/89)
    - Whitefield, Doxie (Box-folder 21/90)
    - Whitfield, Gwendolyn Watts (Box-folder 21/91)
    - Whiting, Rhonda F. (Box-folder 21/92)
    - Whitley, Margaret L. (Box-folder 21/93)
    - Whitted, Burma A. (Box-folder 22/1)
    - Wibecan, Ken (Box-folder 22/2)
    - Wickliff, Aloysius M., Sr. (Box-folder 22/3)
    - Wielawski, Andrew (Box-folder 22/4)
    - Wiester, Carolyn (Box-folder 22/5)
    - Wiggins, Colleen M. (Box-folder 22/6)
    - Wilcox, George (Box-folder 22/7)
    - Wiley, Celeste M. (Box-folder 22/8)
    - Wilkins, Carol (Box-folder 22/9)
    - Wilkinson, Neal H. (Box-folder 22/10)
    - Williams, Barbara Ann (Box-folder 22/11)
    - Williams, Charles (Box-folder 22/12)
    - Williams, Deborah (Box-folder 22/13)
    - Williams, Delores J. (Box-folder 22/14)
    - Williams, Donald (Box-folder 22/15)
    - Williams, J. Samuel (Box-folder 22/16)
    - Williams, John L. (Box-folder 22/17)
    - Williams, Lawrence M., Sr. (Box-folder 22/18)
    - Williams, Marna B. (Box-folder 22/19)
    - Williams, Mary (Box-folder 22/20)
    - Williams, Oneita L. (Box-folder 22/21)
    - Williams, Patricia J. (Box-folder 22/22)
    - Williams, Raymond (Box-folder 22/23)
    - Williams, Roy E. (Box-folder 22/24)
    - Williams, Royshunda (Box-folder 22/25)
    - Williams, Sadie M. (Box-folder 22/26)
    - Williams, Sandra Jo (Box-folder 22/27)
    - Williams, Sir (Box-folder 22/28)
      Includes police report.
    - Williams, Tessie P. (Box-folder 22/29)
    - Williams, William J. (Box-folder 22/30)
    - Williams, Willie M. (Box-folder 22/31)
    - Willie, Oveta (Box-folder 22/32)
    - Willis, Lincoln (Box-folder 22/33)
    - Willis, Mattye (Box-folder 22/34)
    - Willoughby, Robert E. (Box-folder 22/35)
    - Wilson, Freddie L. (Box-folder 22/36)
    - Wilson, Leona (Box-folder 22/37)
    - Wilson, Naomi (Box-folder 22/38)
    - Wilson, Serena (Box-folder 22/39)
    - Wilson, Walter (Box-folder 22/40)
    - Wimmer, J. Fred (Box-folder 22/41)
    - Wise-Love, Gwendolyn (Box-folder 22/42)
    - Wishon, Jane (Box-folder 22/43)
    - Withrow, Noreatha (Box-folder 22/44)
    - Wittemen, Rose (Box-folder 22/45)
    - Witt-Ison, Muriel (Box-folder 22/46)
    - Wock, Jill (Box-folder 22/47)
    - Wolff, Robert W. (Box-folder 22/48)
    - Wong, Elize (Box-folder 22/49)
    - Wood, James P. (Box-folder 22/50)
    - Wood, Nettie Walker (Box-folder 22/51)
    - Woodard, Thad (Box-folder 22/52)
    - Woods, Patricia L. (Box-folder 22/53)
    - Woodward, Jan (Box-folder 22/54)
    - Wooten, Melanie K. (Box-folder 22/55)
    - Wright, Christina (Box-folder 22/56)
    - Wright, Lois M. (Box-folder 22/57)
    - Wunrow, Jeffrey D. (Box-folder 22/58)
    - Wyatt, Tolbert (Box-folder 22/59)
    - Yagami, Richard H. (Box-folder 22/60)
    - Yamamoto, Joyce (Box-folder 22/61)
    - Yancey, Eleanora Allen (Box-folder 22/62)
    - Yancy, Grady, Jr. (Box-folder 22/63)
    - Yancy, Annette (Box-folder 22/64)
    - Yanoff, Jerome C. (Box-folder 22/65)
    - Yarbrough, Eram (Box-folder 22/66)
    - Yellin, Arnold S. (Box-folder 22/67)
    - Yokogawa, Nobuyuki (Box-folder 22/68)
    - Yoshida, Gloria (Box-folder 22/69)
    - Young, Catherine (Box-folder 22/70)
    - Young, Jerrilyn (Box-folder 22/71)
    - Young, Wilson (Box-folder 22/72)
    - Younge, Sammy Leamon (Box-folder 22/73)
      Includes postcard, drama script, and photographs.
    - Zarbin, Earl (Box-folder 22/74)
    - Zendejas, Robert H., Sr. (Box-folder 22/75)
    - Ziglar, Jacqueline Dash (Box-folder 22/76)
    - Zubrensky, Ruth J. (Box-folder 22/77)
      Includes report.
- Series II: My Soul Looks Back in Wonder Interviews, 2003-2004
  The book My Soul Looks Back in Wonder is a collection of essays based on original audio interviews with 33 individuals. Authored by journalist Juan Williams, this book focuses on the experiences of both leaders and ordinary people who participated in or were affected by civil rights movements. Subseries I contains a file for the 82 interviewees (many of whom were not included in the book) and may include emails, transcripts, book chapter drafts, and background research. Subseries II contains the audio recordings of the interviews conducted by journalists, and Subseries III contains photographs of some interviewees. A few of the interviewees for this series were also interviewed on the bus tour; those related items are included in Series III and IV.
  - Subseries I: Interviewee Files, 2003-2004, 84 folders
    - Andrade, Juan Jr. (Box-folder 23/1)
    - Baxley, Bill (Box-folder 23/2)
    - Beal, Gerald K. (Box-folder 23/3)
    - Beerman, Leonard (Box-folder 23/4)
    - Boggs, Grace Lee (Box-folder 23/5)
    - Bonilla, Reuben (Box-folder 23/6)
    - Booth, Heather (Box-folder 23/7)
    - Bourne, St. Clair (Box-folder 23/8)
      2 MS Word .doc files also available.
    - Branch, Raylawni G. (Box-folder 23/9)
    - Braxton, Annye H. (Box-folder 23/10)
    - Brownmiller, Susan (Box-folder 24/1)
    - Carlos, John (Box-folder 24/2)
    - Charles, Michael Ray (Box-folder 24/3)
    - Collins, Wendell (Box-folder 24/4)
    - Davis, L. Clifford (Box-folder 24/5)
    - Dickinson, Jim (Box-folder 24/6)
    - Dinkins, David N. (Box-folder 24/7)
    - Doty, Juanita Sims (Box-folder 24/8)
    - Epps, Jesse (Box-folder 24/9)
    - Fife, John M. (Box-folder 24/10)
    - Fleming, Karl (Box-folder 24/11)
    - Fountain, Clarence (Box-folder 25/1)
    - Frank, Barney (Box-folder 25/2)
      MS Word .doc file also available.
    - Garcia, Isabel G. (Box-folder 25/3)
    - Gields, Clarence (Box-folder 25/4)
    - Goodman, Carolyn (Box-folder 25/5)
    - Graves, Curtis (Box-folder 25/6)
    - Green, Percy (Box-folder 25/7)
    - Gutierrez, Jose Anjel (Box-folder 25/8)
    - Hackney, Lucy Durr (Box-folder 25/9)
    - Halpern, Rosario Salgado (Box-folder 25/10)
    - Harjo, Suzan S. (Box-folder 25/11)
    - Harrington, Penny (Box-folder 26/1)
    - Hayes, Shirley G. (Box-folder 26/2)
    - Hernandez, Joe D. (Box-folder 26/3)
    - Hite, Nancy (Box-folder 26/4)
    - Holland, Endesha Ida Mae (Box-folder 26/5)
    - Horowitz, Rachelle (Box-folder 26/6)
    - Jarrett, Vernon (Box-folder 26/7)
    - Jones, Doug (Box-folder 26/8)
    - King, B. B. (Box-folder 26/9)
    - Kirk, Ronald (Box-folder 26/10)
    - Kochiyama, Yuri (Box-folder 26/11)
    - Kwoh, Stewart (Box-folder 26/12)
    - Kyles, Samuel (Box-folder 27/1)
    - Landrieu, Moon (Box-folder 27/2)
    - Lawson, James, Jr. (Box-folder 27/3)
    - Lee, Sammy (Box-folder 27/4)
    - Lout, James M. (Mike) (Box-folder 27/5)
    - Lowery, Joseph E. (Box-folder 27/6)
    - Lyons, Kenneth (Box-folder 27/7)
    - Mashariki, Job (Box-folder 27/8)
    - McKinstry, Carolyn M. (Box-folder 27/9)
    - McWhorter, Diane (Box-folder 27/10)
    - Mease, Quentin (Box-folder 28/1)
    - Meier, Deborah W. (Box-folder 28/2)
    - Monroe, Sputnik (Box-folder 28/3)
    - Moses, Robert (Box-folder 28/4)
    - Moutoussamy-Ashe, Jeanne (Box-folder 28/5)
    - Murray, Tawanda (Box-folder 28/6)
    - Oldham, Charles R. (Box-folder 28/7)
    - Poussaint, Alvin F. (Box-folder 28/8)
    - Pride, Carlton (Box-folder 28/9)
    - Reid, Vernon (Box-folder 28/10)
    - Rivers, Eugene F. (Box-folder 28/11)
    - Romilly, Constancia (Box-folder 29/1)
    - Rowles, Billy E. (Box-folder 29/2)
    - Seay, Norman R. (Box-folder 29/3)
    - Shores, Barbara and Helen (Box-folder 29/4)
    - Smith, Jerome M. (Box-folder 29/5)
    - Spellman, Toyin (Box-folder 29/6)
    - Steger, Michelle (Box-folder 29/7)
    - Sutton, Goodloe (Box-folder 29/8)
    - Swann-Daniels, Carol (Box-folder 29/9)
    - Tafel, Richard (Box-folder 29/10)
    - Thompson, Larry D. (Box-folder 29/11)
    - Tisdale, Alice and Charles (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Trickey, Minnijean Brown (Box-folder 30/2)
    - Uyeshima, Erin Emiko (Box-folder 30/3)
    - West, W. Richard (Box-folder 30/4)
    - Wilson, Diane (Box-folder 30/5)
    - Wilson, Eddie (Box-folder 30/6)
    - Wunrow, Jeffrey D. (Box-folder 30/7)
    - Yamamoto, Joyce (Box-folder 30/8)
    - Zabel, William D. (Box-folder 30/9)
  - Subseries II: Sound Recordings, 2003, 53 sound discs (minidiscs), 22 sound cassettes and 18 microcassettes
    - AFC 2005/015: SR001, 1 minidisc
      - Carolyn Goodman interviewed by Jimmie Briggs
      - Job Mashariki interviewed by Jimmie Briggs (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR002, 1 minidisc
      - Job Mashariki interviewed by Jimmie Briggs (2 of 2)
      - Juan Andrade interviewed by Jimmie Briggs
      - Tawanda Murray interviewed by Jimmie Briggs
    - AFC 2005/015: SR003, 1 minidisc
      - Charles Oldham interviewed by Jimmie Briggs
      - Jeff Wurnow interviewed by Jimmie Briggs
      - Norman Seay interviewed by Jimmie Briggs (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR004, 1 minidisc
      - Norman Seay interviewed by Jimmie Briggs (2 of 2)
      - Michelle Steger interviewed by Jimmie Briggs
    - AFC 2005/015: SR005, 1 minidisc
      - Percey Green interviewed by Jimmie Briggs
      - Vernon Jarrett interviewed by Jimmie Briggs
    - AFC 2005/015: SR006, 1 minidisc
      - Gerald K. Beal interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski, 2003-10-14
    - AFC 2005/015: SR007, 1 minidisc
      - Ruben Bonilla, Jr., interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Corpus Christi, Texas, 2003-11-05
    - AFC 2005/015: SR008, 1 minidisc
      - Heather Booth interviewed by Megan Rosenfeld, 2003-12-05 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR009, 1 minidisc
      - Heather Booth interviewed by Megan Rosenfeld, 2003-12-05 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR010, 1 minidisc
      - Raylawni Branch interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Hattiesburg, Mississippi, 2003-12-10
    - AFC 2005/015: SR011, 1 minidisc
      - Susan Brownmiller interviewed by Ponchitta Pierce in New York, New York, 2003-11-21 (1 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR012, 1 minidisc
      - Susan Brownmiller interviewed by Ponchitta Pierce in New York, New York, 2003-11-21 (2 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR013, 1 minidisc
      - Michael Ray Charles interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski, 2003-12-03
    - AFC 2005/015: SR014, 1 minidisc
      - L. Clifford Davis interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski, 2003-10-14
    - AFC 2005/015: SR015, 1 minidisc
      - Jim Dickinson interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski, 2003-12-11
    - AFC 2005/015: SR016, 1 minidisc
      - David Dinkins interviewed by Ponchitta Pierce in New York, New York, 2003-12-03 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR017, 1 minidisc
      - Clarence Fountain interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 2003-10-31
    - AFC 2005/015: SR018, 1 minidisc
      - Barney Frank interviewed by Megan Rosenfeld, 2003-11-24
    - AFC 2005/015: SR019, 1 minidisc
      - Rosario Halpern interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Marfa, Texas, 2003-11-20
    - AFC 2005/015: SR020, 1 minidisc
      - Susan Shown Harjo interviewed by Megan Rosenfeld, 2003-12-11
    - AFC 2005/015: SR021, 1 minidisc
      - Joe D. Hernandez interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Temple, Texas, 2003-10-30
    - AFC 2005/015: SR022, 1 minidisc
      - Nancy Hite interviewed by Bonny Wolf, 2003-12-08
    - AFC 2005/015: SR023, 1 minidisc
      - Rachelle Horowitz interviewed by Megan Rosenfeld, 2003-11-24
    - AFC 2005/015: SR024, 1 minidisc
      - B. B. King interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Jacksonville, Florida, 2003-12-27
    - AFC 2005/015: SR025, 1 minidisc
      - Ronald Kirk interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Dallas, Texas, 2003-11-19
    - AFC 2005/015: SR026, 1 minidisc
      - James M. (Mike) Lout interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Jasper, Texas, 2003-10-28 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR027, 1 minidisc
      - James M. (Mike) Lout interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Jasper, Texas, 2003-10-28 (2 of 2)
      - Kenneth Lyons interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Jasper, Texas, 2003-10-28 (1 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR028, 1 minidisc
      - Kenneth Lyons interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Jasper, Texas, 2003-10-28 (2 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR029, 1 minidisc
      - Kenneth Lyons interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Jasper, Texas, 2003-10-28 (3 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR030, 1 minidisc
      - Diane McWhorter interviewed by Ponchitta Pierce in New York, New York, 2003-12-08 (1 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR031, 1 minidisc
      - Diane McWhorter interviewed by Ponchitta Pierce in New York, New York, 2003-12-08 (2 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR032, 1 minidisc
      - Quentin Mease interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Houston, Texas, 2003-11-11 (1 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR033, 1 minidisc
      - Quentin Mease interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in Houston, Texas, 2003-11-11 (2 of 2)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR034, 1 minidisc
      - Deborah W. Meier interviewed by Ponchitta Pierce in Boston, Massachusetts, 2003-11-06
    - AFC 2005/015: SR035, 1 minidisc
      - Alvin Poussaint interviewed by Ponchitta Pierce in Boston, Massachusetts, 2003-11-07 (1 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR036, 1 minidisc
      - Alvin Poussaint interviewed by Ponchitta Pierce in Boston, Massachusetts, 2003-11-07 (2 of 3)
    - AFC 2005/015: SR037, 1 minidisc
      - Carlton Pride interviewed by Joe Nick Patoski in San Marcos, Texas, 2003-11-24
    - AFC 2005/015: SR038, 1 minidisc